<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>


    <string name="caption01" translatable="false">

        1.Sometimes life can surprise you with a happy coincidence.\n
2.The world is full of nice people. If you can’t find one, BE ONE.\n
3.Don’t look for miracles. You yourself are the miracle.\n\n
1.I am a woman, I bend, I don’t break.\n
2.Behind every successful women is herself.\n
3.I’m not beautiful like you. I’m beautiful like me.\n\n

1.I’m no beauty queen, I’m just beautiful me.\n
2.I love the person I’ve become because I fought to become her.\n
3.A strong woman looks a challenge in the eyes and gives it a wink.\n\n

1.Nothing makes a woman more beautiful than the belief that she is beautiful.\n
2.Being yourself is the prettiest thing a person can be.\n
3.Be you because you’re pretty.\n\n

1.The happier you are the more beautiful you become.\n
2.I’m the queen of my own little world.\n
3.Always wear your invisible crown.\n\n

1.Date: Today. To Do: Be Happy!\n
2.Happy is the man who can make a living by his hobby.\n
3.My hobby is my job. it’s a Jobby!\n\n

1.Because every picture tells a story…\n
2.I wish my eyes could take photos.\n
3.Let’s wander where the WiFi is weak.\n\n

1.Let’s find some beautiful place to get lost.\n
2.For a minute there I lost myself.\n
3.Go where you feel most alive.\n\n

1.Stay close to what keeps you feeling alive.\n
2.Once a year, go someplace you have never been before.\n
3.I will go anywhere as long as it is forward.\n\n

1.I am a slow walker, but I will never walk back.\n
2.I’m going to make you so proud. – Note to Self\n
3.Note to self: Please Relax\n\n

1.Don’t be the same, be better!\n
2.Ideas are useless unless used.\n
3.Great minds think differently.\n\n

1.All the best people are crazy.\n
2.There’s always a wild side to an innocent face.\n
3.If I had to describe my personality, I’d say good looking.\n\n

1.I’m always trying hard to improve my selfies.\n
2.When nothing is going right, click a selfie!!\n
3.Be a Warrior not a Worrier\n\n

1.Being happy never goes out of style.\n
2.Happiness is.. to be with you FOREVER\n\n
3.Being with you is what I call happiness.\n\n

1.Friends make you laugh till your cheeks hurt.\n
2.Life is better when you’re with friends.\n
3.Sunday Means Fun Day\n\n

1.Surround yourself with those who make you happy.\n
2.Surround yourself with people who lift you up.\n
3.Sky above me, earth below me, fire within me.\n\n

1.When you are burning inside but you have to keep smiling.\n
2.When life gets blurry adjust your focus.\n
3.When life gives you lemons, make lemonade.\n\n

1.Radiate positive vibes\n
2.Life is way too short for bad vibes.\n
3.Elegance is the only beauty that never fades.\n\n

1.Simplicity is the keynote of all true elegance.\n
2.Simplicity is the essence of happiness.\n
3.Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication.\n\n

1.I always go for simplicity.\n
2.The most complicated skill is to be simple.\n
3.There is beauty in simplicity.\n\n

1.Beautiful things don’t ask for attention.\n
2.I am not alone, because loneliness is always with me.\n
3.Being single doesn’t mean always available.\n\n

1.Don’t let your dreams be dreams.\n
2.Don’t let anyone ever dull your sparkle.\n
3.I smile because I have no idea what’s going on.\n\n

1.I collect smiles and then I give them away.\n
2.Warning: You might fall in love with me!!\n
3.Caution: You might get addicted to me!!\n\n

1.Confidence level: Selfie with no filter!!\n
2.I’m a direct descendant from awesomeness.\n
3..I’m not perfect but I am limited edition.\n\n

1.I may not be the best, but I’m definitely not like the rest.\n
2.I’m not fat. I’m just much easier to see.\n
3.I’m not short, I’m just more down to earth than other people.\n\n

1.I’m not short, I’m concentrated awesome.\n
2.I’m not lazy. Someone just stole my motivation.\n
3.I’m not lazy, I’m just on my energy saving mode.\n\n

1.I’m not fat. It’s just my AWESOMENESS swelling up inside me.\n
2.I’m not fat, god gave me airbags cause I’m precious.\n
3.The only reason I am fat is because a tiny body couldn’t store all this personality.\n\n

1.Sometimes you don’t need a caption, picture says it all.\n
2.Too lazy to think of a caption \n
3.Living my life in my style.\n\n

1.There is great beauty in being yourself.\n
2.If I were you, I would adore me.\n
3.I am In Love With Myself, With My Heart.\n\n

1.Today I choose to be the best version of myself.\n
2.I am in the process of becoming the best version of myself.\n
3.Be the type of person that you want to meet.\n\n

1.The day you decide to love yourself is the day you’ll conquer the world.\n
2.There’s nothing more important than loving yourself.\n
3.In every moment, you are the only one who gets to choose your attitude.\n\n

1.Sometimes you have to be your own hero.\n
2.You have to be ODD, to be number ONE.\n
3.Be a Fruit Loop in a world full of Cheerios.\n\n

1.Be a beautiful cupcake in a world full of muffins.\n
2.Coffee and Friends make the perfect blend.\n
3.We go together like cupcakes and frosting.\n\n

1.We go together like coffee and donuts.\n
2.We go together like peanut butter and jelly.\n
3.We go together like cookies and milk.\n\n

1.We go together like salt and pepper.\n
2.We go together like a burger and fries.\n
3.Every time I see you, I fall in love all over again.\n\n

1.Every time I see you smile, I fall in love all over again.\n
2.I can guarantee. You won’t find nobody else like me.\n
3.I am what I am. I am my own special creation.\n\n

1.I’m built from every mistake I have ever made.\n
2.If you don’t like where you are, MOVE. You are not a TREE.\n
3.Never announce your moves before you make them.\n\n

1.Feel the Fear and Do it Anyway.\n
2.Take the risk or lose the chance.\n
3.Take every chance, drop every fear.\n\n

1.Say YES to new adventures.\n
2.The best memories comes from the craziest ideas.\n
3.It’s kind of fun to do the impossible.\n\n

1.Make life fun, tomorrow isn’t guaranteed.\n
2.Life is about right now in this very moment. Not tomorrow, not yesterday but now. Live it!\n
3.I’m enjoying this look.\n\n

1.Never looked so good…\n
2.Fall in LOVE with my new look.\n
3.I’m loving it!!!\n\n

1.A good life is a collection of happy moments.\n
2.Live the life you’ve imagined!\n
3.Live for the moments you can’t put into words.\n\n

1.We do not remember days, we remember moments.\n
2.Capture the moment.. It lives forever..\n
3.Every moment matters.\n\n

1.This moment will never come again.\n
2.Any day spent with you is my favorite day. So today is my new favorite day.\n
3.Home is wherever I’m with you.\n\n

1.Always better together.\n
2.I’m glad that you and me are US!\n
3.Gravitation is not responsible for people falling in love.\n\n

1.Love isn’t something you find. Love is something that finds you.\n
2.Love is life. And if you miss love, you miss life.\n
3.Life is not perfect but every second with you is.\n\n

1.When I am with you I feel perfect.\n
2.Love has no limits.\n
3.There is no remedy for love but to love more.\n\n

1.Grow old along with me! The best is yet to be.\n
2.The best is yet to come.\n
3.DIFFERENT doesn’t mean WRONG.\n\n

1.Be the change that you wish to see in the world.\n
2.If you resist change, you resist life.\n
3.It is not how much you do – how you do it is what makes life beautiful.\n\n

1.Be your own kind of beautiful.\n
2.Be brave enough to live different.\n
3.Don’t be like the rest of them darling.\n\n

1.Happy girls are the prettiest.\n
2.Don’t forget to smile \n
3.A smile is a curve that sets everything straight.\n\n

1.The most wasted of all days is one without laughter.\n
2.Cherish every moment of your life.\n
3.Enjoy the little things in life.\n\n

1.The most important things in life aren’t things.\n
2.Do small things with great love.\n
3.Make every second count.\n\n

1.Do what makes you happy!\n
2.Be thankful for the life you own.\n
3.We only have one life to live.\n\n

1.To live is the rarest thing in the world. Most people exist, that is all.\n
2.Don’t just Exist. Live.\n
3.Live Every Moment, Laugh Every Day, Love Beyond Words.\n\n

1.Cherish the things that money can’t buy.\n
2.Nothing can bring you peace but yourself.\n
3.To find yourself first learn about yourself.\n\n

1.Find yourself and be that.\n
2.Let’s just be who we really are.\n
3.Think positive. Live positive.\n\n

    </string>
</resources>